>> 演讲者 1: 为什么要培养不是依赖关系 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So
why is breeds not a dependency?
> > Brian Holt: 所以，就像这里的品种一样。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So breeds,
as in this breeds right here.
>> Brian Holt: 不是依赖关系。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Is not a dependency.
我想这里的名字有点不正确
I guess this is kind of misnamed
right here, breeds right there.
我们可以称这类品种如 API 品种或类似的
We could call this breeds,
like API breeds or something like that
>> Brian Holt: 我们开始吧。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There we go.
这可能是你之前很困惑的
So that could've been
confusing to you before.
这不依赖于品种因为这些品种
It doesn't depend on
breeds because this breeds
在此处未使用此 useEffect 的任何位置。
is not used anywhere inside
of this useEffect right here.
从这个效应的任何地方都没有读出来，对吧 ?
It's not read from anywhere
inside of this effect, right?
现在设定品种是吧
Now set breeds is, right?
所以这才是这里的原因
So that's why this is in here.
但 API我只想让你记住这些品种和品种是分开的
But API, I just want you to keep in mind
this breeds and that breeds are separate.
他们不一样对吧
They're different things, right?
因此，它从未在使用中使用，因此它不依赖于它。
So this is never used inside of use effect
so therefore it's not dependent on.
>> Brian Holt: 是吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah?
>> 扬声器 1: 组件中的任何问题是否都不构成这些生命周期
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Was there any problem
with component did not amount those life
循环方法?
cycle methods?
为什么会创建挂钩 ?
Why did hooks get created?
> > Brian Holt: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Well, okay.
>> 演讲者 1: [COUGH] >> Brian Holt: 相信挂钩
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: [COUGH]
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There's a belief that hooks
比要了解组件的生命周期更简单
are simpler than having to learn
the life cycle of components and
要理解像上下文之类的事情
having to understand like context and
some other things like that.
你可以注意到我的语言不是很拘谨
And you can notice I'm being
non-committal with my language.
因为我对这些 API 的效果有多大的怀疑
It's because I have my doubts about which
of these APIs is gonna be for the better,
也许我们会在稍后谈论分类组件时讨论这个问题。
and like maybe we'll address that a bit
later when we talk about class components.
可能是这样吧
That's probably the better so
每个人都能站在同一网页上
that everyone can kind of
get on the same page here.
但简单的答案是人们认为这很容易，而且
But the short answer to that is
people think that this is easier, and
那我就教你们俩，你可以是你想用的法官。
then I'll teach you both, and you can be
the judge of which one you want to use.
但是，没有，阶级成分也没有固有的问题。
But no, there's no there's no inherent
problem with class components.
>> Brian Holt: 没有限制。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There's no limitations.
实际上，类组件可以做更多的挂钩。
Actually, class components
can do more than hooks can.
>> 演讲者 1: 当前 >> Brian Holt: 当前。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Currently
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Currently.
他们有计划弥补缺口但现在
They have plans to fix the gaps,
but as of right now
还有一些钩子不可能做到的
there's still some things
that hooks can't do.
所以我们应该把它叫做我们在这里做的事情。
So one more thing we should
call it that we did here.
所以如果我选择像美国的爱斯基摩犬然后切换到猫
So if I go and select like American Eskimo
dog and then switch to Cat,
很快就会把它转换成默认选项，对吧 ?
notice it very quickly switches that
back to be the default option, right?
这是我们在这里用空字符串做的事情。
That's something that we did
here with this empty string.
>> Brian Holt: 通常这只是一种理解，但我只想说
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Normally it's just kind
of understood, but I just wanna call out
一旦我把它调为空字符串就因为
the fact that as soon as I call setBreed
here to be empty string, because of
这种反应的方式和我们在思考的方式
the way of the reactive stretch and
the way that we're thinking about this.
这一情况一旦确定，这一动物就会被下降到这里。
As soon as this is set, this is synced
to this animal drop down down here.
或者说是在我把它送到空串的情况下
Or rather the breed drop down, that as
soon as I send that to empty string,
它马上就会在这里繁殖对吧
it immediately updates breed right here,
right?
所以这些是连接在一起的，我们一起克隆在一起。
So those are connected together,
we've clung that together.
所以现在真的很酷只要我们确定我们是在
So now it's really cool as long as we're
making sure that we're calling setBreed in
在适当的地方，它将这种效应从所有地方
the right places, that it cascades that
effect down to all the places that
取决于这些信息对吧
are depending on that information, right?
那就是钩子之类的东西只要你在玩
So that's the power of hooks and stuff
like that is as long as you're playing by
React 规则，您可以免费获取此传播状态。
the React rules you get this
propagation state for free.
所以我想告诉你
So I wanna tell you that useAffect and
useState 是您要使用的两个主挂钩。
useState are the two primary
hooks that you're gonna use.
这将覆盖 90 % 的用例。
That's gonna cover about
90% of your use cases.
所以 useState 很明显，最常见的使用效果也是相当普遍的，
So useState obviously the most common
use effect also being quite common, and
也许就像 useRef 偶尔
then maybe like useRef occasionally, and
还有一长尾的钩子你可能永远不知道
then there's a long tail of other
hooks that you may never have to know.
所以我们肯定还是会谈他们的，我们会进入一个中间的反应。
So we'll definitely still talk about them,
we'll get into an intermediate React.
我想我们还是会在这里谈的，但那就好了
I think we'll still talk about Ref
in here, but that'll be it for
React 主机的 React 生命周期以及类似的内容。
the React life cycle of the React host and
things like that.